If you are looking for a life insurance solution that
maximizes protection value
per premium and provides stable
long-term savings, then a universal life insurance product
is the solution you are looking for.
Today I'm going to unbox with you a
life insurance product
from Bruden Show with many outstanding benefits.
PRU universal life insurance products offer
maximum protection value per
premium.   By
setting aside just one month's salary to
pay for an annual insurance premium, you'll have
dozens of times that amount in insurance coverage to protect
against the biggest risks.
For example, Ms. Nguyen Thi A, 30 years old,
allocates approximately 20 million VND from her monthly salary
to pay the one-year fee for her contract.   The
insurance payout she received was 1.6 billion
VND, equivalent to 81 months' salary.   The
PRU universal life insurance product
offers two insurance plans to
choose from depending on your protection needs: a
basic plan and an
enhanced plan.  If you're trying to
balance risk mitigation and saving
for your family's future, a
basic insurance plan might be a good choice.  If you
prioritize protecting your
family from unforeseen events, you should choose an
enhanced insurance plan.  With a
basic insurance plan, the main product benefit
will be the greater of 100% of
the sum insured and the basic account value
plus the value of any additional premiums
.  And with the enhanced insurance plan
, the main product benefit will be equal to
100% of the sum insured plus the
base account value and
any additional account value.  Getting insurance is
a long-term plan.  During
that time, of course,
your family's protection needs may change.  You
can flexibly adjust your insurance plan to your
liking.
Alternatively, if your family faces
short-term financial difficulties, you can exercise your
flexible premium payment option from the fifth year of the contract
or withdraw funds from the contract account value
as needed.
These flexible benefits will
allow you to proactively manage your
finances when needed while still maintaining
financial protection for your family.
Especially during important events, you
are guaranteed an increase in your insurance coverage
without reassessment, helping you
prepare a contingency fund according to your
financial capabilities and meet the need for
increased protection for your family.  Once
children have grown up, the expenses of
raising them also decrease.  You
might have some extra money then.  And you
can use this surplus to accumulate more,
helping you reach your retirement plan faster
.  So
what attractive savings options does this product offer?  A portion of
your annual premium will be accumulated, and the
total accumulated amount will have the opportunity to
grow steadily at the
actual investment interest rate announced by Prudential,
which will not be lower than the guaranteed interest rate
.  If you want to accumulate even more,
you can also proactively pay additional
insurance premiums to earn interest at the same rate as the
base account value, along with
attractive bonuses.  Customer appreciation bonuses
,
contract retention bonuses.
You quickly achieved
your savings goal.
In addition, you can combine
optional enhanced protection benefits
at a reasonable cost to further protect your
family.
Find the perfect solution for
your family today.